{
    "id": "560c82047e42413cb9d8b2692276d0ec",
    "title": "Mistakes With Verbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "All day I was ................................... a sweater.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "putting on",
                "wearing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c92c5043422645d198f454ec468703c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ................................... my car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "disposed of",
                "disposed off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9b008892ffeb483eb4ee8df6c9db97f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ................................... this painting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "look at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "90c51d25a65c4193b8b06666419fd759"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ................................... a new computer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ordered",
                "ordered for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "078762e77e1c410c8d983cf69c1262b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why donâ€™t you ................................... me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f7be137a948465fa206533b35a4a48c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He came ....................................... a blue jacket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wearing",
                "putting on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e20e4a2f2861455cba7cab559e786add"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................... to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "denied",
                "refused"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7bb0b385388242f4b58b5ec60d2867d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................... there for a day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lived",
                "stayed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c1566dd7e57411ab479ba3791bf5399"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................. no mistake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "committed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0565dae178341fe995bf5e5aa566264"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ought to ............................... exercise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "take"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0236ae9a79347beb88e6e4fc151031f"
        }
    ]
}